fileresearchcenter.com 2018-05-08

# FileResearchCenter.com - Privacy Policy

**_Last Updated_ : December 23, 2016**

 **Privacy Policy**

Support.com respects your privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of your Personal Information that you may submit to Us by telephone, when using our websites, online services, software or during the performance of remote computer support services provided via telephone or online by Support.com, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliated entities ("Support.com", "We", "Our" or "Us"). "Personal Information" is information that (i) is recorded in any form; (ii) is about you or pertains to you, and (iii) can be linked to you. Personal Information includes information like your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and other information that is associated with the foregoing. Personal Information does not include information We may collect that does not identify you ("Other Information"), such as how many devices use a particular operating system or how many customers experience a certain kind of technical problem. 

We recognize that when you choose to provide Us with information about yourself, you trust Us to act in a responsible manner. Support.com has created this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") to inform you how your Personal Information will be treated if you use Our websites, software or services. In general, you can visit Our websites without telling Us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. 

Support.com's authorized partners ("Partners") may use Our software or online services to provide their services to you ("Partner Services"). Partner Services may be governed by the respective Partner's privacy policy, which terms may differ from this Privacy Policy. 

Support.com has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Policy and Our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through the support.com website and does not include information collected from Our software or services. 

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that We have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

**Information We Collect and How We Use it**

We collect Personal Information in a variety of ways, including when you subscribe to one of Our newsletters, download a trial version of a product, or receive a product or service from Us or one of Our distribution partners or from a service provider who licenses one of Our remote support systems, such as Support.com® Cloud. The type of information We collect may vary based on the way We interact with you. For example, if you sign up for a newsletter or download an evaluation version of Our software, We may only collect your name and email address. However, if you make a purchase from Us then We may also collect your credit card number over the phone, and we may collect your phone number and physical address in order to complete the purchase, verify your identity and deliver any physical products. We may combine information We have about you with information We obtain from business partners or other companies. If you provide Us with any Personal Information relating to other people, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

We use Personal Information and Other Information to provide you with the products or services you have requested, process any payments you have agreed to for such products and services, contact you regarding specific products or services you have requested, provide other information you have requested from Us, customize advertisements or content you may see while using Our products or services, and, if you have agreed to receive special promotional offers from Us by email or otherwise, to contact you regarding such promotional offers. Support.com may also display or provide you with targeted content or promotional offers based on Personal Information; and from time to time We may use Personal Information to offer you products or services. We may also use Personal Information for other business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying Our services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of Our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding Our business activities. 

During your use of Our website, software and services, Our systems may also collect Other Information from your device and network that is not used to identify you, but is helpful in Our efforts to provide the features or services you have requested. This includes information such as the type of computer and processor you are using, which version of the operating system is installed, the configuration of your computer in terms of other application programs used, your computer's Media Access Control address, whether any security software is installed and if it is up-to-date, the names, makes and models of other devices on your network, and information on how you use Our products. For example, Support.com automatically receives and records information on Our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Support.com cookie information, and the webpages you request. This is done as part of regular internet communication between a browser and a website. We use this information to provide the services and functions you request, and to improve Our product and service offerings in the future. We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where We are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it for the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information as detailed in this Privacy Policy. 

**CONSENT AND CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER**

BY USING OUR WEBSITES, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE PRIVACY POLICY. OUR WEBSITES, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES ARE CONTROLLED AND OPERATED BY US FROM THE UNITED STATES AND ARE NOT INTENDED TO SUBJECT US TO THE LAWS OR JURISDICTION OF ANY STATE, COUNTRY OR TERRITORY OTHER THAN THAT OF THE UNITED STATES. FOR THOSE OF YOU VISITING US FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, CANADA, OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES, PLEASE NOTE THAT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU ENTER WILL BE TRANSFERRED OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN UNION OR YOUR HOME COUNTRY FOR USE BY US AND OUR AFFILIATES FOR ONE OR MORE OF THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THE PRIVACY POLICY, TO THE UNITED STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS THAT MAY HAVE DIFFERENT DATA PROTECTION RULES THAN THOSE OF YOUR COUNTRY. YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED AND STORED IN THE UNITED STATES, AND AS A RESULT, GOVERNMENTS, COURTS, OR LAW ENFORCEMENT OR REGULATORY AGENCIES MAY BE ABLE TO OBTAIN DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION THROUGH LAWS APPLICABLE IN THE UNITED STATES. BY USING OUR WEBSITES, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES AND PROVIDING US WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU CONSENT TO THIS TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. 

**Children**

This website is not aimed to attract children and its objective is not to collect Personal Information from children. Anyone under the age of 18 should not use this website unless supervised by an adult. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Support.com does not rent, sell or share Personal Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when We have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliated companies and entities (SDC Services Canada Inc., Support.com India Private Limited, Support.com Philippines, Inc.) for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Please note that Support.com software is published under the Support.com, Sammsoft or SUPERAntiSpyware brand. Sammsoft and SUPERAntiSpyware are trade names for certain software products developed by or for Support.com. We reserve the right to use information about you in accordance with the Privacy Policy for all Support.com subsidiaries and divisions and under all Support.com trade names.
  * To service providers who work on behalf of or with Support.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your Personal Information to help Support.com communicate with you (for example, email service providers). These companies, however, do not have any independent right to use or share this information.
  * As We believe to be necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable law or legal process, which might include laws outside your country of residence, or to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including those outside your country of residence, for the purposes of meeting national security or law enforcement requirements, subpoenas, or court orders, or establishing or exercising Our legal rights or defending against legal claims.
  * As We believe to be necessary or appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Support.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We may transfer information about you in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). 

**Tracking Technologies**

Support.com and its marketing partners, affiliates, analytics providers, or customer support providers use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and local shared objects such as Flash LSO, HTML5 and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about Our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for Our shopping cart, to remember users' settings, and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use Our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of Our website may be limited. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. You may manage Flash cookies at: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

As is true of most websites, We gather Other Information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track users' movements around the website and to gather demographic information about Our user base as a whole. We may combine this automatically collected log information with Personal Information We collect about you. We do this to improve the services We offer you, and to improve marketing, analytics, and website functionality. If We combine Other Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your location), We will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined. 

We partner with third parties to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other websites. Our third party partners may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of this interest-based advertising, you may visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info/ to learn about opt-out options. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads. 

**Choices and Access**

If you wish to subscribe to Our email updates, We will use your name and email address to send the email to you. You may choose to stop receiving Our marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails. 

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to Support.com, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of an established business relationship, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

You can access, edit and request deletion of your Personal Information stored by Us at any time by utilizing web services, if available, or by contacting Us via one of the methods listed at the end of the Privacy Policy. In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal Information suppressed from Our database or otherwise let Us know what limitations you would like to put on Our use of your Personal Information. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send Us your request, and We may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. 

We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase, you may not be able to change or delete the Personal Information provided until after the completion of such purchase). There may also be residual information that will remain within Our databases and other records, which will not be removed. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

**Retention Period**

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with Our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce Our agreements. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to Personal Information about you to employees and contractors who We believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help protect Personal Information We collect about you from unauthorized use or disclosure. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on Our order forms, We encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, We cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on Our website, please contact Us at [privacy@support.com](mailto:privacy@support.com). 

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Support.com. This Privacy Policy does not address, and We are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which We may link. The inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by Us or by Our affiliates. If you submit Personal Information to any of those other websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. 

**Social Media Widgets**

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These features may collect your IP address and identify the page you are visiting on Our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on Our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Sensitive Information**

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the website or otherwise to Us. 

**BBB Code of Business Practices**

Your privacy is important to Us. As a Better Business Bureau Accredited Business, We have made a commitment to follow the BBB Code of Business Practices, including the requirement to safeguard your privacy. Further information about this program is available at <http://www.bbb.org/us/Business-Accreditation/>. If you feel that We have violated your privacy, you may contact the BBB at: <http://www.bbb.org/us/Business-Complaints/>. 

**Privacy Complaints**

Support.com commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and Our collection or use of your Personal Information. Individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding the Privacy Policy should first contact Support.com at the address shown under "Contact Us" below. 

**Privacy Complaints by Swiss Citizens**

In compliance with the Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Support.com commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and Our collection or use of your Personal Information. Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding the Privacy Policy should first contact Support.com at the address shown under "Contact Us" below. 

Support.com has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB Swiss Safe Harbor, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Support.com, please visit the BBB Swiss Safe Harbor website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Support.com may update the Privacy Policy at any time. If We make material changes We will notify you about significant changes in the way We treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address in our file for you or by placing a prominent notice on Our website prior to the changes becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on Our privacy practices. The "LAST UPDATED" legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes will become effective when We post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Your use of the Services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please email Us at [privacy@support.com](mailto:privacy@support.com) or write to Us by post at: 

Support.com, Inc.  
900 Chesapeake Drive, 2nd Floor  
Redwood City, California 94063  
Attn: Privacy
